lankapropertyweb.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy Policy | LankaPropertyWeb

Lanka Property Web (Pvt) Ltd ("us", "we", or "our") operates the LankaPropertyWeb.com website & LankaPropertyWeb App (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from LankaPropertyWeb.com

The privacy of our visitors to LankaPropertyWeb.com is important to us. 

At LankaPropertyWeb.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit LankaPropertyWeb.com, and how we safeguard your information.  We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site.  This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as My Account.

We also use third party advertisements on LankaPropertyWeb.com to support our site.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Colombo real estate ads to someone in Colombo, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into accounts.

## Information we collect from you

We may collect and process the following information about you:

**Information you provide to us**
    You may provide us with information in several ways, including by filling in forms on our websites or on our apps or by corresponding with us by phone, email and live chat. This includes information you provide when you register for an account or subscribe, Post ad ad, contact advertisers using forms or phone numbers available on our websites or apps, post in our forums/comments, register for an event, enter a competition, promotion or survey, provide feedback or report about an ad.
    This information may include any information you add to your profile (for example, your name, address, email address, phone number, profile picture and user name). 
**Information we collect about you**
    When you use our websites or apps, we may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

## Use of Data

We use the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain the Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer care and support
  * To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
  * To monitor the usage of the Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues

## Disclosure Of Data

### Legal Requirements

We may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Lanka Property Web (Pvt) Ltd
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

### **Sharing your data with third parties**

Should you register for any of our events, we may pass your contact information to parties that are partners in the event in question. We may also share your details under special circumstances such as when we believe in good faith that it is required by law. Apart from that we will not share your data with any 3rd party entity. 

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## **Asking us to remove your personal information**

If you do not want to receive information from us in the future you can quickly ask us to stop emailing you by clicking the unsubscribe link you will find on many of our service and marketing e-mails or by sending your details to  **contactus@lankapropertyweb.com**

If, additionally, you want us to remove your information entirely (and assuming we have no other obligation to keep it) please let us know by emaling us on **contactus@lankapropertyweb.com** and we will execute this within 7 working days.

## Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: **contactus@lankapropertyweb.com**
